ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Photographs /4289 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Photographs
1996-2009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Alumni Affairs and Development
/4289 P
10.06 cubic feet
10.1 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection of photographs come from several events and groups in the ILR School. We have photographs from the Groat & Alpern Award receptions, Commencement, Alumni Awards, and many photographs of the new ILR building, faculty, Alumni, and Alumni Association.
7145210
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 08, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collection of photographs come from several events and groups in the ILR School. We have photographs from the Groat & Alpern Award receptions, Commencement, Alumni Awards, and many photographs of the new ILR building, faculty, Alumni, and Alumni Association.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4083: ILR School Alumni Association Files /4118 MB: ILR School Alumni Memorabilia /4119m: ILR School Richard Jacobstein Memorabilia /4120: ILR School Alumni Scrapbooks /4130 AV: ILR School Alumni Weekend Audio-Visual Materials /4130 MB: ILR School Alumni Weekend "Reunion" Book Memorabilia /4289 AV: ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Audio-Visual Materials /4289 PUBS: ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Publications
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Photographs; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Alumni Affairs and Development -- Photographs.
7145210
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  26 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  28 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  21 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  15 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2008 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  37 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  32 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  27 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2009 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  29 photographs
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2009 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2009 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Groat & Alpern Awards - 3/29/2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- ILR Building Photos (Box 1, Folder 28)
  34 slides
- ILR Building Photos (Box 1, Folder 29)
  20 slides
- ILR Building Photos (Box 1, Folder 30)
  19 slides
- ILR Building Photos (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Michael Landsbury, Jefferson Cowie -- OSS (Box 2, Folder 1)
  26 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Michael Landsbury, Jefferson Cowie -- OSS (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Michael Landsbury, Jefferson Cowie -- OSS (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ILR Alumni, ILR Commencement (Box 2, Folder 4)
  19 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- ILR Commencement, ILR Alumni (Box 2, Folder 5)
  25 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- ILR Alumni Awards Program - 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Institute for Workplace Studies (Box 2, Folder 7)
  11 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Misc. photos (Box 2, Folder 8)
  20 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Phase II - Dedication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  21 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Misc. photos (Box 2, Folder 10)
  32 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Union Day 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  4 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Raynor Career (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Raynor Career (Box 2, Folder 13)
  34 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Union Days (3/31/2000), Bruce Raynor/Ed Lawler (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1999/2000 Welcome Event (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Random" Construction Photos (Box 2, Folder 16)
  27 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- "Random" Construction Photos (Box 2, Folder 17)
- "Random" Construction Photos (Box 2, Folder 18)
  13 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Unknown pics - some pictures are at Johnson Museum (Box 2, Folder 19)
  8 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- 2003 Groat Awards? Cerand Sibling & Elizabeth Moore (Box 2, Folder 20)
  2 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Fall 2002? Board Weekend - Ithaca Campus (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fall 2002? Board Weekend - Ithaca Campus (Box 2, Folder 22)
  14 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- April 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Random Photos (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Misc. photos (Box 2, Folder 25)
  36 photographs -- reorganized - was box 1
- Commencement 2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Woman Speaker - Rm 305 Ives (Box 2, Folder 27)
- ILR Homecoming Oct. 13, 2007 (Box 3)
  - ILR Homecoming Oct. 13, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (1 of 14) (Box 4)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (1 of 14) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (2 of 14) (Box 5)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (2 of 14) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (3 of 14) (Box 6)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (3 of 14) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (4 of 14) (Box 7)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (4 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (5 of 14) (Box 8)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (5 of 14) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (6 of 14) (Box 9)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (6 of 14) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (7 of 14) (Box 10)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (7 of 14) (Box 10, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (8 of 14) (Box 11)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (8 of 14) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (9 of 14) (Box 12)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (9 of 14) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (10 of 14) (Box 13)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (10 of 14) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (11 of 14) (Box 14)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (11 of 14) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (12 of 14) (Box 15)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (12 of 14) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (13 of 14) (Box 16)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (13 of 14) (Box 16, Folder 1)
- ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (14 of 14) (Box 17)
  - ILR Celebration 2006 -- 30 March 2006 (14 of 14) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- ILR Bench Donor Family Reunion 2006 (Box 18)
  - ILR Bench Donor Family Reunion 2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Alpern 60th Anniversary -- 15 Nov. 2006 (Box 19)
  - Alpern 60th Anniversary -- 15 Nov. 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- 2005 Groat and Alpern Awards -- Mar. 31,2005 (Box 20)
  - 2005 Groat and Alpern Awards - Mar. 31, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 21)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 21, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 22)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 23)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 23, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 24)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 24, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 25)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 25, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 26)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 26, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 27)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 27, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 28)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 28, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 29)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 29, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event and NYC Board Meeting (Box 30)
  - ILR Alumni Assoc. -- 13 June 2006 -- Welcome Event (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Sage Hall Fall Scenics (Box 31)
  - Sage Hall Fall Scenics (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Student Govt. Group Photo -- 11/30/2005 (Box 32)
  - Student Govt. Group Photo -- 11/30/2005 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- MILR Gathering NYC - Cornell Club -- 8 May 2008 (Box 33)
  - MILR Gathering NYC - Cornell Club -- 8 May 2008 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Caption three piece mural (Box 34)
  - Caption three piece mural (Box 34, Folder 1)
- MOU Signing (Box 35)
  - MOU Signing (Box 35, Folder 1)
- MOU Signing (Box 36)
  - MOU Signing (Box 36, Folder 1)
- ILR Reunion '04 -- all images (Box 37)
  - ILR Reunion '04 -- all images, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Katz CD 1 -- Trustee Council -- 10/27/2006 (Box 38)
  - Katz CD 1 -- Trustee Council -- 10/27/2006 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- ILR Building Photos -- 2008 (Box 39)
  - ILR Building Photos -- 2008 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Katz CD 2 -- Trustee Council -- 10/27/2006 (Box 40)
  - Katz CD 2 -- Trustee Council -- 10/27/2006 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Bench Donor Family Reunion 2006 (Box 41)
  - Bench Donor Family Reunion 2006 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Not labelled (Box 42)
  - Not labeled (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Not labelled (Box 43)
  - Not labeled (Box 43, Folder 1)
- 2006 Graduation (Box 44)
  - 2006 Graduation (Box 44, Folder 1)
- 2007 Alumni Association Round table (Box 45)
  - 2007 Alumni Association Round table (Box 45, Folder 1)
- New Building Shots Aug. 2009 (Box 46)
  - New Building Shots Aug. 2009 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Conference Center Opening Celebration -- Oct. 15, 2004 (Box 47)
  - Conference Center Opening Celebration -- Oct. 15, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- ILR Building Photos -- 2008 (Box 48)
  - ILR Building Photos -- 2008 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- ILR Reunion 2008 (Box 49)
  - ILR Reunion 2008 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- 2005 Groat Awards (Box 50)
  - 2005 Groat Awards (Box 50, Folder 1)
- 2004 Groat and Alpern Awards (Box 51)
  - 2004 Groat and Alpern Awards (Box 51, Folder 1)
- ILR Martin Scheinman Dedication -- Oct. 19, 2007 (Box 52)
  - ILR Martin Scheinman Dedication -- Oct. 19, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Graduation Celebration 2007 (Box 53)
  - Graduation Celebration 2007 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- 2006 (Box 54)
  - 2006 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Unlabeled (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Rose Batt images (Box 56)
  - Rose Batt images (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Paul Cole Photos (Box 57)
  - Paul Cole Photos (Box 57, Folder 1)
- ILR School - Groat & Alpern Awards -- 29 March 2007 ( 3 of 3) (Box 58)
  - ILR School - Groat & Alpern Awards -- 29 March 2007 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- ILR School - Groat & Alpern Awards -- 29 March 2007 (2 of 3) (Box 59)
  - ILR School - Groat & Alpern Awards -- 29 March 2007 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- ILR School - Groat & Alpern Awards -- 29 March 2007 (1 of 3) (Box 60)
  - ILR School - Groat & Alpern Awards -- 29 March 2007 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- ILR Holiday Card (Box 61)
  - ILR Holiday Card (Box 61, Folder 1)
- ILR Reunion 2007 (Box 62)
  - ILR Reunion 2007 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Arcitecture & Ed's Farewell -- 8/18/2005 (Box 63)
  - Architecture & Ed's Farewell -- 8/18/2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Ed Gray Reception Photos -- 9/2005 (Box 64)
  - Ed Gray Reception Photos -- 9/2/2005 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Milton Konvitz (Box 65)
  - Milton Konvitz (Box 65, Folder 1)
- ILR Lack Program (Box 66)
  - ILR Lack Program (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Boca Raton & La Events -- Pat Wright Seminar (Box 67)
  - Boca Raton & La Events -- Pat Wright Seminar (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Nick Salvatore (Box 68)
  - Nick Salvatore (Box 68, Folder 1)
- 2/28/2008 -- Katz Webinar presentation (Box 69)
  - 2/29/2008 -- Katz Webinar presentation (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Negatives - June 2006 - NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Print pictures - June 2006 - NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 2)
  26 photographs - reorganized was box 1
- Print pictures - June 2006 - NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 3)
  26 photographs - reorganized - was bx 1
- Print pictures - June 2006 - NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 4)
  26 photographs - reorganized was bx 1
- Print pictures - - June 2006 - NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 6)
  22 photographs - reorganized was bx 1
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Print pictures - June 2006 -- NYC Board Meeting & Welcome Event (Box 70, Folder 12)
  19 photographs - reorganized was bx 1
- 2006 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  4 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Homecoming Tailgate - Oct. 2007 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  12 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Misc. photos (Box 70, Folder 15)
  17 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Misc. photos (Box 70, Folder 16)
  2 photographs - reorganized was box 2
- Ed Gray Reception Photos - 9/2005 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  2 photo-copies - reorganized was bx 2
- Milton Konvitz & ILR Lack Program (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Maurice Neufeld, Ed Lawler, Liz Moore (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Faculty of ILR (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Scheinman Dedication (Oct. 2007) (Box 70, Folder 21)
  2 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Nick Salvatore; Boca Raton; Katz Webinar (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Windmuller Dedication - 11/2008 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  27 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2008 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  26 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2008 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  10 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- ILR Homecoming tailgate - Oct. 13, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  26 photographs - 26 photographs - was bx 2
- ILR Homecoming tailgate - Oct. 30, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  21 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- ILR Reunion 2006 -- Groat 2006 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  36 photographs -- reorganized was bx 2
- ILR Reunion 2006 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  24 photographs -- reorganized - was bx 2
- Celebration - 2005 - Groat (Box 71, Folder 7)
  reorganized - was bx 2
- 2004 Groat and Alpern Awards (Box 71, Folder 8)
  16 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Misc. photos (Box 71, Folder 9)
  3 photographs - reorganized - was bx 2
- Misc. photos (Box 71, Folder 10)
  1 photograph - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat 2000 -- William Kay II; Francis N. Bonsignore; Robert H. Bluestein (Box 71, Folder 11)
  18 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat 2000 - William Kay II; Francis N. Bonsignore; Robert H. Bluestein (Box 71, Folder 12)
  19 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat 2000 -- William Kay II; Francis N. Bonsignore; Robert H. Bluestein (Box 71, Folder 13)
  24 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat 2000 - William Kay II; Francis N. Bonsignore; Robert H. Bluestein (Box 71, Folder 14)
  26 photographs -- reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2003 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  34 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  24 photographs -- reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  33 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  25 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Groat Awards 2006 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Grad Celebration 2009 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  3 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- ILR Grad Celebration 2006 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- ILR Grad Celebration 2006 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- ILR Grad Celebration 2006 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- ILR Grad Celebration 2006 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- ILR Grad Celebration 2006 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  9 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Graduation Celebration 2007 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Graduation Celebration 2005 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Graduation Celebration 2007 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- ILR 50th Anniversary Celebration - Dean's Panel (1996) & Reunion (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Homecoming/Tailgate Party - Oct. 1999 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  6 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Homecoming Tailgate 10/2001 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  23 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Homecoming Tailgate 10/2001 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  13 photographs - reorganized was bx 2
- Reunion 2001 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- Reunion 2001 (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Reunion 2001 (Box 72, Folder 26)
- ILR Alumni Grad Celebration - 4/26/2009 (Box 73)
  - ILR Alumni - Grad Celebration - 4/26/2009 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    removed from box 72, ff 11